giftbig.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy & Policies | GiftBig.com

**A.  ** **General Usage**   
This Privacy Policy explains how QwikCilver collects, uses, discloses and protects your Personal Information, obtained explicitly through www.giftbig.com website (" **Site** "), as well as other information collected automatically without direct submission by you. 'Personal Information' is information that enables anyone to contact you and your credit-card details. Your full name, address, IP address, e-mail address are other examples of Personal Information. 

You may need to provide QwikCilver your Personal Information during the course of using some services of the QwikCilver; for instance, while registering on the website and while making an online purchase. 

QwikCilver may use the information submitted by you to send you e-mails for administrative purposes. QwikCilver does not make these e-mail addresses available to any third party. QwikCilver DOES NOT trade or sell your Personal Information in any manner, except as is provided under Section III (B) below, or if express consent is sought from you. 

When you use the Site, QwikCilver's servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about your activities on the Site; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information you submit to QwikCilver. The anonymous information will be used for QwikCilver's understanding of how the Site is used and for other statistical purposes, for system administration and to personalize your experience. QwikCilver may also collect information related to access times, browser type, and your IP address for tracking usage patterns and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms. 

QwikCilver may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Site, but it will never contain Personal Information. QwikCilver does not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations. However, in situations when QwikCilver is legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties, QwikCilver will do so. 

QwikCilver implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks.

**B.   ****Shared Personal Information**

You are required to submit your personal information at the time of making an online purchase of QwikCilver Gift Cards. QwikCilver uses an online payment gateway that is operated by a third party and the personal information that you share with QwikCilver is transferred and shared with such third party payment gateway operator. The said operator may also have access to your online purchase history/details that you make from [www.giftbig.com](http://www.giftbig.com/=/).

You are required to submit your personal information at the time of making an online purchase of QwikCilver Gift Cards. QwikCilver uses an online payment gateway that is operated by a third party and the personal information that you share with QwikCilver is transferred and shared with such third party payment gateway operator. The said operator may also have access to your online purchase history/details that you make from [www.giftbig.com](http://www.giftbig.com/=/).

Extremely sensitive information like you credit-card details are transacted upon secure sites digitally under encryption, thereby providing the highest possible degree of care are available as per current technology. You are advised, however, that Internet technology is not 100% safe and you should exercise discretion on using the same.

**C.   ****General**

QwikCilver will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization.
